teleprofitsnow.com 2011-02-21

# ProfitAM.com Privacy Policy

First let us say, we completely respect your privacy. This document explains our policy relating to any of your personal data that you provide to us. ProfitAM.com headquarters are at 5510 NE Antioch Rd #105, Gladstone, MO 64119. The website [www.newsaminvestigates.com](http://www.newsaminvestigates.com/) is owned by a 3rd party company in partnership with ProfitAM.com ("the Site"). By using this Site you agree that all personal data that you supply to us will be true, complete and accurate in all respects and you agree to notify us immediately of any changes to that personal data. We will deal with your personal data in compliance with all current protection legislation. Please note this applies only to ProfitAM.com not to other companies' or organizations' websites to which we link or allow to advertise here. Personal data will be collected, processed and used by ProfitAM.com for the purposes of providing ProfitAM.com’s services and products to you and the other purposes mentioned below. We may hold personal data relating to the transactions you enter into with others (such as an online seller) or us through this Site. 

We will not disclose personal data to any party outside ProfitAM.com and associated partners. We may use personal data to let you know about products and services that may be of particular interest to you. We may also want to provide you with related information from third parties that we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please complete the form by [clicking this link](http://www.newsaminvestigates.com/unsubscribe.html). 

We will not sell your personal information (other than as part of a sale of the whole or a substantial part of the assets of ProfitAM.com). ProfitAM.com may disclose your personal data acting in good faith if it believes such action is necessary: to conform with a legal requirement or comply with the legal process, protect and defend the rights or property of ProfitAM.com, enforce this online agreement, act to protect the interests of its users. We use cookies (information stored by your browser) to track information on the pages read by visitors to this site to improve the content and offerings on this site. Although we cannot identify individuals from this information, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. Cookies can be disabled on your computer, but this may limit the experience that our website is able to offer. When you register for any of ProfitAM.com’s services, newsletters, mailing lists, competitions or promotions we will require information identifying you so that we can provide the service requested. We may ask our registered website users to take part in surveys or opinion polls. Participation is always voluntary and on occasion may offer an opportunity to win prizes as a thank you for your time and effort. Our success relies on our recommending the best products and services available. To help us ensure we make the very choices we may from time to time analyze the data that we hold and such analysis may be made to find out what is most likely to appeal to individuals and web-site users. Also, we may provide aggregate statistics about our visitors, sales, browser type, operating system, Internet, domain, demographic and profile data, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information. We hope that this will provide you with a more interesting experience. We may provide your information to our customer service agencies for similar purposes. We or our agents and sub-contractors may occasionally contact you including by post, email or telephone to tell you more about products and services or to ask you for your feedback and comments on our products and services. 

By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this Policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the web site, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it. Continued use of our services will signify that you agree to any such changes. From time to time, this Site may include links to other web sites. We may not be operating the linked sites and we do not necessarily endorse the contents, views or products of the linked sites. We do not accept any responsibility for use of the linked sites. You are advised to use linked sites with caution and with due regard to any terms of use on those sites. If you transfer to other sites by using a link from our Site to theirs we may receive aggregate or otherwise anonymous statistical information about your trip and any purchases you may make on those sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or content of other web sites and your visit to those sites is not protected by our privacy policy. WE TAKE PRECAUTIONS WITH CUSTOMER INFORMATION AND PERSONAL DATA, HOWEVER, EXCEPT IN THE CASE OF DEATH OR PERSONAL INJURY RESULTING FROM OUR NEGLIGENCE, We DO NOT ACCEPT RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE RESULTING FROM ANY SECURITY BREACHES THAT MAY OCCUR. It is important for you to let us know if you think that the data we have about you is inaccurate or incomplete. You may remove your information from our database by completing the form by: [clicking this link](http://www.newsaminvestigates.com/unsubscribe.html). If you have any questions about the handling or protection of your personal data or your rights under this online agreement please contact us by writing to:   
ProfitAM.com  
5510 NE Antioch Rd #105  
Gladstone, MO 64119  
(816)453-8836

Third Party Advertising & Cookies  
Some ads appearing on this website are delivered by our Web advertising partners. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party ad server, or individual advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personally identifiable information), may be used to serve ads to you on this and other sites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.
